105, 106, 107...
Toriko has had a life full of misfortune-tori.
It felt like things changed when she met Fuwari, but...
I was wrong-tori!
That's because this morning, Fuwari is...
Midorikaze!
Are you really...
Even though I've only known you all for a short while,
you've helped me in so many ways.
But, I'll be heading back to the Palps.
Really?!
Genius
What's That-panda?
Genius? What's That-panda?
You're heading back to the Palps?!
Are you serious?
Yeah.
How sudden!
What brought this on?
I gave up becoming a princess.
That means I'm no longer a princess scholarship student.
So I'm pretty sure that Hibiki won't let me stay.
No way!
It's true you may have originally come here
as a princess scholarship student,
but are you sure you really
want to leave the school?
She's absolutely right!
But...
In that case, why not attend school
as a regular student like the rest of us?
She's right.
Good idea!
We'd be like a school of fish attending school together!
Not like that.
What are you, dense?
I appreciate it, but...
What do you want to do, Fuwari?
Me?
The goats want to know, too!
And me!
How do you really feel?
I...
PriPara truly is a lot of fun and I really enjoyed it.
And I became good friends with Toriko and all of you.
I really would like to stay...
Then stay!
We've become such good friends,
I don't want to say goodbye!
But...
I'm sure that Hibiki won't forgive me.
Let us through!
Master Hibiki won't see you without an appointment.
Isn't there something you can do?!
Then...
Max Beam!
I humbly decline.
Why?!
We need to talk to Lord Shikyouin about something!
I demand you let us pass!
That's right!
Please let us see him! Please let us see him!
He's a regular person!
Ladies, please calm down.
Would you please...
Acting Headmaster!
Andou...
Please let Fuwari continue attending school.
Please!
Whether she'll be staying or not...
She was the one who decided that.
Yes, I did, but...
I really would like to continue if you'd let me stay!
I see.
But didn't you already make your decision?
Isn't it bad to be so indecisive?
If I may have a word, Acting Headmaster.
I'm sure you're familiar with Paprika Private Academy school rule, number 157:
Paprika Private Academy
"Don't worry about it at night,
worry about it in the morning", correct?
Don't worry about it at night, worry about it in the morning
All humans make mistakes.
You don't think the best at night.
That's right.
Since Midorikaze thought it over
and decided she would like to stay here,
I believe her desire should be respected.
Please!
So that's how it is.
Since it's a rule my grandfather made,
I'll respect it.
Hooray!
Isn't that great, Fuwari?!
It is! Thanks!
An approval capisce!
Isn't that great, goats?
Another case closed!
Thank you, everyone.
So that's Houjou Sophy and Toudou Sion...
Why is he staring so much?
Is he planning to get in our way?
This time, I'll take them!
Wow!
For... For you to be forced to live in the attic...
What a lovely room!
What?!
This room is wonderful!
I'm so close to the sky!
I-Is that so?
Then that's good.
It's a pity that you decided to give up
the princess candidacy, Miss Midorikaze,
but your manner lessons won't stop
just because you're a normal student now.
Make sure you're prepared!
Yes, of course.
You say that, yet you're barefoot!
It seems they've brought their favourite bed.
They're crazy strong.
But that'll never fit...
And on top of that, school rule number 82:
"Moving school furniture is prohibited"!
Here's your first insubordination ticket!
How unfortunate.
I'll just give you a present to replace it with!
A futon of grass.
Better?
How's that, Fuwari?
It feels great!
Thanks!
That's great!
Rina, let's clean up!
Take this!
And this!
Pushuu...
There we go.
We're done!
Move complete!
Thank you, everyone.
I really appreciate it.
I'm moved to tears.
Your move-in pizza from Papa's Pasta has arrived!
All right!
I was getting hungry.
Since you won the Summer Dream, you'll be having
your début concert as Dressing Flower tomorrow!
Please eat this and put on a good show tomorrow, Fuwari.
Thank you!
Same goes for you guys!
Acknowledged!
- Capisce!
Fuwari, you're not leaving after all-tori?
Nope.
I'm sorry I worried you like that.
You're really not-tori?
Yeah, I'm not.
Really really?
Really.
Is this really really happening?
It is.
Tori!
Tori! Tori! Tori! Tori! T—
It's not a dream-tori!
Toriko isn't used to being happy,
but now she's insanely happy-tori!
Let's keep working together.
Tori!
I can't wait for tomorrow-tori!
Capisce!
The delicious hamburger place closed down?!
Closed
It's a message from the gods,
telling you to only eat meat buns.
That makes Mikan a little sad...
Man! I overslept!
You're late, Laala!
I'm super sorry!
Oh?
Ah!
Fuwari just went in Prism Stone with everyone else!
Closed
H-Hey! Let's go!
I'm not going to miss today's show, too!
Now then, give us a good show again today.
Please scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your coord.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Coord Change Start!
Another performance in the coord that
greatly contributed to your winning the SummDrea!
Surprise Summer Adventure Coord!
Go!
Yeah!
I wonder what they've got in their numerous pockets.
Love?
Or maybe their dreams?
Perfect Summer Adventure Coord!
While searching for that answer,
they start their friendship-filled performance!
Unforgettable Summer Adventure Coord!
Ladies and ladies,
thank you for waiting.
The debut concert for our Summer Dream
winners is now starting!
The girls chosen this time have opened a path
to perform in next year's parade with this coord.
Take a look!
They may be the five girls chosen
to ring the Bell of Miracles.
You won't want to miss seeing such wonderful ladies.
You'll want to completely...
...let it soak and...
...absorb into your heart.
All right, let's call them out here.
Okay!
Let us get this underway.
Now introducing Dressing Flower.
Dressing Flower is the best!
Hey, everyone!
We're Dressing Flower!
We've got a full house!
Thanks for joining us!
We won't let you down!
We're awesome, aren't we?!
We're the best in PriPara now!
Dorothy...
Do you wanna see show like ours?
We do!
Capisce!
Thanks!
Now then, please listen to...
"Unforgettable Summer Adventure"!
Dream Theatre Show, switch on!
Laala! Fuwari! Do-Re-Sion!
Yeah!
Summer's here
Let's go on an adventure
There's a heap of things we want to do
That we want to know
We get a treasure map in the darkness
And we suddenly come across a giant watermelon?!
Our hearts beat like crazy
At the familiar striped pattern
Dead or alive
What's happening up ahead?
There's no time to waste
Let's dive right in!
It's an unforgettable summer adventure
All right, everyone! We're all stocked up!
Let's make use of this happiness
Raise our arms, and push up toward the blue sky!
It's a surprising summer adventure!
Isn't it an awesome view?
It is!
This was well worth the thrill
Go for it!! Hey! Hey! Let's dance!
Airy Change!
No matter what, you all will
You all will stand above the rest, always and forever!
It's an unforgettable summer adventure!
Cyalume Airy!
All right, everyone! Let's get fired up!
Don't leave! Don't give up!
Flap your wings! Let it all out!!
It's an unrestrained summer adventure
Yodeleihi!
Even the wind is with us
Let's go wild! Let's go even further!
Thank you!
Tension max!
Go for it!! Hey! Hey! Let's dance!
Relax!
Higher, higher, and even further up
Let's Go!
Until you've reached the place you've been aiming for
Ring the bell as a signal
Ding dong! Ding dong! Go Go!
Let's ring the bell of everyone's dreams!
Everyone's dreams have become one!
Echo! Charm Bell!
Fuwari!
Thank you, everyone!
Let's have a thunderous applause for Dressing Flower!
Please keep your eyes on these five in our upcoming Autumn Dream Idol GrandPrix!
Huh?
Our coords changed?!
Our Summer Dream Parade Coord vanished!
The wings which soar through the sky...
When they are spread,
a sole Lilium Casa Blanca shall bloom in the darkness.
Tonight is the first act of Masquerade Time.
My name is...
...Phantom Thief Genius!
Phantom Thief Genius-pri?
Give our coords back!
Is this some sort of attraction-kuma?
No, this is no attraction.
It's a guy-pri!
You're right.
A guy?!
Huh?!
A guy...
A guy?
No way!
Huh?
Our coords!
Give them back, you perv!
Why such aggression?
This coord is not for those
who are undeserving to wear it.
Undeserving?
Who-panda? Who-panda?
But we got it by winning!
Absolutely false!
Stealing Dream Tickets, among other things,
is strictly prohibited here!
Oh my!
It's a stand-off between two pretty boys!
That means this has to be...
Huh?
I can see your true colors.
Oh?
You're a complete narcissist, aren't you?
Wha...
While that may be true...
Which one?
Assuming there are times
when you are just too perfect...
Yes?
It's only natural to love oneself.
He has a point-pri.
Oi!
Ah! Give them back!
Those girls won those fair and square-pri!
Give them back!
You can't eat them!
You dirty thief!
That's right-tori!
That's right-kuma!
What makes you so important-usa?!
Pushuu...
Pri!
Panda! Panda!
We're all friends?
We're all idols?
That way of thinking here in PriPara ends today.
Huh?
What?
Heed this!
Starting tomorrow, PriPara will no longer be
for playing at being friends,
but for measuring raw ability.
Friends will fall to the wayside,
and instead you'll be facing off as enemies.
Wait!
Trying to get away?!
What are these?
A card?
He's escaping-panda!
I won't let you!
How dare he!
Area B2, clear-panda.
Nothing in B2-panda.
Nothing in A5-panda.
Too many-panda.
We must not let him get too far-panda.
No reports of where he has gone-panda.
Where'd he go-panda?
He vanished?!
What about the coords?!
Unfortunately, they've been stolen.
Then does that mean we
won't be able to be in the parade?!
Over this...
...stylish...
...tough...
...guy's...
...dead body will I let him get away with this!
Even though we made a mistake
and let him slip by this time...
Why has he come to PriPara despite being a guy?
What is his goal?
Please wait for us as we
thoroughly investigate this incident.
It feels like that guy will show up again
at the next Grand Prix-pri.
Next time, I'll steal your heart.
Autumn is just around the corner.
Don't worry.
I'm sure that by the time the Autumn Dream
Idol GrandPrix arrives, this will have been solved...
by Meganii.
Leaving it to someone else, huh-kuma?
But if you don't find him...
We're all friends?
We're all idols?
Got it!
I'll do my best to wait until then!
Laala!
I'll make sure that we all stay friends!
And I'll make sure that
Phantom Thief Whatever It Was understands that!
It's Genius-pri.
I would also like to have
Mr. Phantom Thief understand.
I won't let him get away with saying
we're just playing at being friends!
Capisce!
Pri!
Go!
Yeah.
Gel!
Devi!
And if we happen to find
the mysterious thief somewhere,
that'll be the end of the line for him!
We'll make sure to capture him!
Pri!
We're counting on you, Meganii!
We'll do everything we can.
Seal these away.
Next episode
I'm back, Laala!
Falulu!
Welcome back capisce!
Welcome Back
Falulu    UnIcorn
I decided to visit since
I'm on summer break!
I'm so glad to see all of you again.
I've been so looking forward to this!
Are you doing well, Unicorn?
Of course!
Actually, we're not the only ones who came back-dechu.
Oh? Who else came?
You'll have to wait and find out-dechu.
Next time:
Falulu Has Returned-dechu!
Falulu Has Returned-dechu
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!
Dechu!